akahitutors.org 2019-06-21

# Akahi Tutors Privacy Policy | 2019/2020 Post UTME Admission Screening, Tutorial

Effective: February, 2015 | Last Modified: July, 2015 

About Akahi Tutors   
Akahi Tutors is one of the leading tutorial centre in Ile-Ife, Nigeria, and an online information and Communication  portal for aspirants, students, graduates and interested individual of various level. Readers and Members of this website can communicate with others using the comments box, ask questions and give answers to question asked by other readers.

Akahi Tutors cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at   [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Information Collection and Use by Akahi Tutors  
Akahi Tutors collects user submitted information such as name, email address, Yahoo ID to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Akahi Tutors service.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. It is important to note that the updates, newsletters or news will be that containing information about the individuals community only or improvement of any of or services (which the user has already paid for).

From time to time, www.akahitutors.org or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on www.akahitutors.org. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Links   
akahitutors.org contains links to sites. www.akahitutors.org is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on www.akahitutors.org

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information   
www.akahitutors.org users may not be able to modify or remove any of their personal comments after posting. www.akahitutors.org is not responsible to readers comments on www.akahitutors,org therefore readers should be careful not to contact the wrong person using this website.

Third Party Advertising   
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by www.akahitutors.org or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.akahitutors.org and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Special Note About Google Advertising  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own [privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Sharing and Disclosure of Information www.akahitutors.org Collects   
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, www.akahitutors.org will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by www.akahitutors.org, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce and protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. www.akahitutors.org reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of myschool.com.ng or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy   
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Contacting the Web Site   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call:08038644328
